From her greatest enemy came her greatest love.
In Tranzit is a drama, romance, war film directed by Tom Roberts.
Nazi POWs suspected of heinous acts are locked up in a Soviet
women's prison run by vengeful female guards.
To weed out the guilty, the innocent must pay.
Can supposed enemies turn into great loves?
Based on a true post-World War II story, this drama stars Thomas Kretschmann, John Malkovich and Vera Farmiga
in a bitter game of cat and mouse and a battle between hate and humanity, mercy and revenge.
Natalia, played by Vera Farmiga.
Max, played by Thomas Kretschmann.
Pavlov, played by John Malkovich.
Klaus, played by Daniel Brühl.
Zina, played by Natalie Press.
Peter, played by Patrick Kennedy.
Tranzit may refer to:
FC Tranzit, a football club in Latvia
In Tranzit, original title of the 2008 Russian-British film In Transit
Tranzit
Group, a bus operator in New Zealand
TranZit, a map of zombies in Call of Duty: Black Ops II
a bar at the No Sleep Festival in Serbia
The film explores themes of prisoner of war, soviet
union, post world war ii, 1940s.
The tone is emotional.